Police!
-Hands on your head!
-Go on!
Nobody move!
-Police!
-They've got an automatic!
-Hands on your head!
-Rear secured.
-Get on the floor!
-Police!
-Confirmed.
-Stay calm.
-Police!
-Police. open up!
Police. open up!
Explosive set.
Three.
Two.
One.
"Valère in position!" "Okay. here I go."
Someone's waiting for you at the entrance.
Okay. Cédric. do you think that
for the next drill. I could--
Listen. Max.
You're a good teammate. honestly.
Really. I mean it.
In two weeks. your future will be decided.
Whatever it is. it won't be with the GIGN.
My job is to be section leader
without David and you. okay?
It's pointless for me to include you.
But take a break. Go see your visitor.
RESTRICTED AREA
WARNING
ELECTRIC FENCE
ELITE FORCE
This is Manon's voicemail…
I told her to leave her phone on.
She didn't.
Is she at the conservatory?
Is she at Nina's? Are they together?
-Do we need to--
-I'll take care of Manon.
Stop worrying and go to work.
Besides. I have a secret mission.
I want to become section leader
of stay-at-home dads.
Whether that's in Paris or Hong Kong.
It's all the same to me.
Singapore.
Hong Kong. Singapore. either works.
-So. should I go?
-Yeah. go ahead. I've got this.
-Your phone.
-Right.
-Your coffee.
-Thanks. That's sweet of you.
I love you.
Your father had just joined
the Gendarmerie with David.
He hadn't met Jess yet.
We were kids. We weren't even your age.
Laurent went on a four-month assignment
to New Caledonia.
I had my job. I couldn't go with him.
A few days after he came back.
I noticed my period was late.
I took a test. I was pregnant with you.
We cried with joy.
Our families thought we were too young.
We didn't care.
The day you were born
was the happiest day of our lives.
You were growing up.
Laurent and I wanted you to have
a little brother or sister.
So we tried again.
For weeks. for months. But it didn't work.
We went to see a doctor.
and that's when we found out.
Laurent had never been able to have kids.
Until then. I always thought
Laurent was your father.
Why are you telling me all this?
So I'll forgive you. is that it?
To say. "I get it. it's no big deal"?
I don't need you to forgive me.
You're my greatest achievement.
I'm not sorry.
But you lied to me.
You cheated on Dad. With David.
Why didn't you tell me after he died?
Would it have helped you if I had?
I didn't tell you to protect you.
Of course it would.
I have a dad who's alive!
I had a right to know.
I kept David away from you.
What?
Your father died
because David went to talk to him.
How dare he approach you after that?
Because we slept together.
once. 25 years ago?
You took my father from me.
Do you realize that? How dare you?
Fuck.
Max.
Shit.
Yeah?
David. it's Valère.
Do you know where your daughter is?
What's going on? Why do you ask?
Her conservatory.
Hostage situation.
We don't know who's inside.
FRENCH ARMY
Approaching. Target confirmed.
Sir. please.
Okay. it's fine.
Fox 1 in position.
Fox 3 in position.
Delta 5 to command.
The entrances are rigged.
Identification in progress.
Hovering in position above the target.
Speak with command.
Establish a list of hostages.
-Okay.
-A quick briefing.
I'll check the van out front.
It hasn't moved in 24 hours.
Okay. sure. Quick briefing.
They arrived on site yesterday night.
They have assault rifles.
They're masked and ready.
They started shooting at 9:00 a.m.
Two were injured but managed to escape.
No updates from the terrorists since.
We think they're holed up inside.
I have three support units.
They're on the station roof. Okay?
Have we identified the Oscars?
Any minute now.
Status on the assault?
Not yet. I don't have enough visibility.
Do we have a 55 on the targets?
Are we in contact with them. at least?
They're not answering.
They're well-prepared.
Thanks. David. I know what I'm doing.
Worryingly. they have hostages
but they haven't made any demands.
We don't know their plan
but we know what to do.
Be ready to move in.
Let's go!
Come on. guys. let's go!
-Get me in touch with command.
-I'll call them.
I need that hostage list. guys.
Wait. here it is.
We have the list.
Please print it out.
Yeah. I'm on site.
We don't know if she's in there.
What do you know?
Not much. to be honest. I just got here.
I'll keep you posted
as soon as I find out.
Okay. Well. the thing is.
I can't get hold of
her friend Nina either. so…
-Wait.
-They're…
She's in there.
Not my baby.
Jess.
I'll get her out of there. Jess.
I promise. You hear me?
I promise. I'll call you back.
No. wait.
David!
What are you doing?
Thinking of going alone?
Let us handle it.
We know what we're doing.
Really? If you know what you're doing.
why didn't you set up an entry team?
We don't know how many there are.
Entrances are rigged. We can't get in.
I didn't say to send in an entry team.
just set one up!
If you need one and you haven't set it up.
that's 30 seconds lost.
We don't even know where they are!
We don't have CCTV or contact.
and we don't know what they want.
Hey. I'm not stupid.
I know Manon's in there.
You're not in charge here. I am. Okay?
Let me do my job.
Don't worry. Cédric.
I know you're in charge.
You know what?
You manage your team. I'll manage myself.
Stop. for fuck's sake.
You know I can't let you go. Stop.
Don't touch me!
For fuck's sake. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Cédric.
You're emotional.
That's normal. You can't think straight.
You have to trust me. okay? Look at me.
We'll get all the hostages out. Unharmed.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
Want to be with us? Focus.
You're the only one who knows
the layout inside. Can you do this?
I'm with you.
Okay. let's go.
Get back to work. Show time's over.
According to witnesses. several masked men
who were heavily armed
took conservatory students hostage
at around nine o'clock this morning.
A security perimeter has been set up.
We don't have any further information
on the operation.
We're waiting to find out
if they've set up a direct line
or opened negotiations
with the hostage-takers.
We don't know the names or demands
of the hostage-takers.
-Okay. got it. Thank you.
-Guys.
I have a helicopter hovering.
but not for long. We'll have to move fast.
I've sent out a drone.
All the entrances to the building
are rigged.
It's all glass. so we're visible.
Except here.
There's one blind spot.
And here in green
are all the telecom lines.
If we can plug into them. we could access
all the cameras in the building.
-Is that the rest of the network?
-Yeah.
Plug in here. Entry team here.
Valère. take part of Section 1.
Set up an entry team there.
Okay.
I'll need one of Chloé's guys too.
Sure. Rapha. can you go with Valère?
-Of course.
-Take any equipment you need to tap in.
Okay.
I'll go back to tracking the van.
Okay. let's go.
Cédric gave me the okay to come.
I'm sorry about Manon.
She's my little sister.
We'll get her out of there.
Hang in there.
Yeah. I'm coming.
I'm not moving. sir.
Back up. I've told you three times.
She's with me.
Okay.
Open up. guys.
Alright. focus. Time to lock in. guys.
Let's go.
It's my daughter. I'm staying.
Jess. stay in the car.
Okay.
I'll be back.
With Manon.
I know you will.
Yes. family members
are starting to arrive on the scene.
A psychological support unit
has been set up.
Obviously. there's shock and confusion…
We're in through door three.
Fifty meters from the lobby.
How's it going. Cédric?
We should be plugged in any minute now.
We'll have the live feed. Valère?
-Your status?
-We're entering the lobby.
Backup in position.
Okay. in position.
Okay.
Let's plug in.
Connecting.
Link established.
-We're in.
-Oscars and Tangos in the auditorium.
Three armed Tangos. Nine Oscars are hooded
and grouped together.
Check the other cameras.
We're under fire!
-Rapha!
-Two men down. I repeat. two men down.
-Valère. take cover! Go back in!
-They're shooting!
You're gonna be okay. Rapha.
Sniper!
They're shooting!
Rapha. are you okay? Can you hear me?
-Fuck.
-It must be coming from next door. Cédric.
We're evacuating. Quick!
Go ahead.
Guys. two pairs with me!
Valère. can you hear me?
-Stay with me.
-Let's move. Come on!
Keep going.
-We're evacuating. Two wounded.
-Fuck!
Confirmed. shots fired
from the building next door.
Under fire at the east entrance.
David. report position.
Have you taken cover?
-We're in.
-Wait…
Secure the position. I'm sending backup.
Reposition towards east entrance.
I repeat. reposition…
We just heard isolated shots
followed by bursts of automatic fire.
The GIGN must be entering the premises.
She's bleeding out.
we need to apply pressure.
-We need a pulmonologist.
-I'll call them.
Hold the pelvis down.
Good. they're loading them now.
All right. we're good.
Okay.
You have the second victim.
-I'm listening.
-All right.
Look at me. You're going to be fine. okay?
-Rapha!
-I've got her!
Okay. are you good?
We need you. okay? You'll be fine.
Keep your eyes open. It's okay.
She was shot in her right side.
You'll be fine. Rapha.
Ma'am. can you hear me?
-Give me the gauze pads.
-Gauze pad.
Go on.
Come on. open your eyes. ma'am.
Squeeze my hand.
Ma'am. open your eyes.
Open your eyes if you can hear me.
-Careful.
-I can take over.
You're with the paramedics.
Stay with us. ma'am.
-Ma'am. open your eyes.
-Open your eyes.
Open the gates! It's leaving!
Clear!
-Clear!
-Go!
Wait. Schwepps. Wait.
Let's check the roof.
It seems that GIGN officers were injured
in an exchange of gunfire in the building…
Chloé. look at this camera feed.
Two more are up there.
Cédric. there are five Tangos
in the auditorium.
There it is.
I tracked down the van.
It left a warehouse in Ivry
yesterday morning.
Okay. we're on it.
Rico. come here. take over for me.
Come on. let's go.
Shut the fuck up!
Cédric.
The terrorist is on the line.
She wants to talk to David.
-David?
-Yeah. I'm listening.
We've got the terrorist on the line.
It's a woman. We'll be listening in.
She wants to talk to you.
Okay. put her on.
Connecting.
You know very well that this is personal.
The GIGN took everything from me.
France took everything from me.
But you? You took my daughter.
My blood. my husband. my family.
I'm a dad too. I'll go get your daughter.
Amal Mayard?
Commander Berger.
Fuck.
Like I said.
it's personal between you and me.
I'm not here to negotiate. David.
Today. I'm going to take
everything from you.
And the whole world
will be there to see it.
Fuck.
In the military.
she specialized in long-range shooting.
I'll take care of Amal.
Let's go. guys.
It's a suicide mission.
She'll execute the hostages.
We have to move in now.
Fuck.
It's nothing.
-Show me your arm.
-I'm fine!
I have to examine you. It's my job.
See. it's nothing. Nothing at all.
-Is he fit?
-Of course.
-Everyone in the Sherpa.
-You're good.
Guys! Listen to me. please.
They have CL20 inside the building.
We can't let them trigger the detonator.
Remember our motto.
"A commitment to life. to all lives."
But there are some situations
where we can't do that.
So. Valère. Djibril. PJ. Nico. Max.
I'll need your shooting skills
because to save the hostages.
we'll have to shoot.
But we'll only have one shot.
So when you shoot. don't miss.
This is a very delicate operation.
Let's make sure
we all go home tonight. please.
Alright. everyone in!
Come on. guys! Go!
-Will you be okay. Valère?
-Yeah.
-Miss Explosive?
-Yes.
Take care of the CL20.
All set. I'm sticking with Intel.
Okay. guys. let's go.
Hello?
Chloé. on the CCTV.
can you see the targets going in?
Affirmative.
Can you see them coming out?
Negative.
Fuck. They still managed to fire at us
from the building next door.
So. there must be…
I don't know. an accomplice?
An underground passageway.
Cédric. we're splitting up.
Okay. guys. Change of plan.
We're looking for a tunnel.
Schwepps. go down that corridor.
We'll meet at the end.
Sergio. you guys take the third floor.
I'm 15 minutes out.
I'll call you from the warehouse.
Copy that. Sending in the Sherpa.
Cédric?
Any news about Rapha?
She's in good hands.
I need you with me. You know how it goes.
If a teammate goes down. you keep moving.
If you can't do that. get off the truck.
We're in building B.
Man down in corridor S.
Team 1. still in corridor V.
Nothing to report on our end.
Team 2. nothing to report in corridor D.
Crossing over to building A.
Fatality confirmed.
Separate columns.
Freeze!
Turn around slowly.
Your weapon on the ground.
Hands on your head.
No!
Not like this.
I want him alive.
He's going to see it all.
He's going to find out how it feels.
You're surrounded.
Your men will all be killed or arrested.
It's over.
It won't be over until I say so.
We're on the roof.
There are still five terrorists in there.
Three with hostages. two on the stairs.
Fire support snipers in position.
Okay.
Section 1 ready to enter the auditorium.
David. do you copy?
Fuck! We found him.
David!
Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
-Can you get up?
Yeah.
We're returning to corridor N.
Thank you. Come on.
On my mark. Three seconds to fire.
Snipers. report status when ready.
One ready.
Two ready.
Three ready.
Four ready.
Five not visible.
Okay. Everyone stay on their target.
Max. let us know when you're ready.
You give the go-ahead.
Target five exposed.
Start the sequence.
One ready.
Two ready.
Three ready.
Four ready.
Five ready.
Countdown. Three seconds.
Three.
Go!
Police!
No one moves!
Okay. we're clear!
Target one neutralized.
Target two neutralized.
Attention. priority alert.
Two men down in corridor S.
Amal wounded. I'm in pursuit.
Five terrorists down. Confirmed.
Tanya. stay with me.
Everyone else. evacuate the hostages.
We found the rest of the CL20 stock.
We're evacuating the hostages.
do you copy?
Check their identity and evacuate.
Tanya. how's it looking?
The last Oscar is handcuffed
to the device.
It's all wired to a timer.
The countdown hasn't been activated.
The handcuffs could be rigged.
It's clearly a remote trigger.
Oscar nine. Okay.
Oscar four. Okay.
David. Amal must have a trigger on her.
Oscar seven. Okay.
Oscar eight. Okay.
Don't do that.
Manon.
It's Cédric.
It's going to be okay.
Put it down.
You think you've won?
Just like me.
you'll lose everything.
Right now.
No!
Fuck. Cédric. the countdown just started.
Five minutes. We need to evacuate
the conservatory now.
All sections. evacuate immediately.
Hostages first. I repeat. hostages first.
Copy that.
We're evacuating them via building B.
Eight identified. none injured.
Oscar 3 is missing.
Come on. We're leaving.
Follow the officers. hurry up.
Come on!
Who's Oscar 3?
Cédric. tell him.
It's Manon.
Hey. Manon. It's going to be okay.
It's going to be okay.
Okay. stay with me. Breathe out.
Breathe.
Something weird about this setup.
-I'll deploy a jammer and secure Manon.
-Okay.
Guys!
Everyone out! There's enough of us.
We've got this!
-Tanya. how long?
-Four minutes.
You never listen. do you? Come on. focus.
Come back to me. Breathe with me.
Just got a hit.
Storage unit 237 belongs to Amal Mayard.
Okay. we're on site.
I'm setting up the jammer.
Manon. you've got to trust me.
It's going to be okay.
Come on.
-Manon. did they put something on you?
-I don't know.
Just look at me.
Okay. it'll be alright.
-Dad.
-Hey.
Are you okay? Yes?
-Awesome. How much time?
-2:30.
2 minutes 30.
What happened?
Do you like it? I look like a badass.
Should I keep it?
At one minute. we'll have to get out.
What does he mean?
We'll all have to get out.
that's what he means.
-Right?
-Yeah.
We're with the best. We're with Tanya.
You know her. She's lethal. Okay?
Do you know where she's from?
No? Nobody else does either.
Cédric. you don't know. do you?
We've reached the second floor.
We're heading towards storage unit 237.
Max. you can go.
It's okay. my love.
Get moving. Now.
I'm staying put.
Clear. There's no one in here.
Fuck.
Manon is secure. I need the bolt cutters.
-Okay.
-What for?
-We're going to get out. We'll run.
-What's happening?
-I can't run. I'm too tired.
-I'll carry you.
-Tanya. talk to me.
-My legs hurt.
-We're not taking any risks.
-It's okay.
-We cut her free and run. Okay?
-Come on.
All right. go. run!
Fuck. she's the one who killed Kröller.
LINA MAYARD: A LIFE CUT SHORT
Go!
Dad. put me down. it's fine.
Come on!
Fuck.
David?
Where's Jess?
It's Jess.
Do you copy?
David.
It's Jess. Jess is the target.
David. do you copy?
Subtitle translation by: Alison Simpson